Carl W. Ackerman Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General Correspondence, 1907-1970 (Box 26-33)
  - Kennan, George (1845-1923)
  - Kennedy, Joseph P.
  - Kerr, Philip
  - King, Willard V.
  - Knollenberg, Bernard
  - Knox, Frank
  - Kospoth, B. F.
  - Krock, Arthur
  - "L" miscellaneous
  - La Guardia, Fiorello H.
  - Landon, Alfred M.
  - Lansing, Robert
  - Latimer, S. L., Jr.
  - Lawrence, David
  - Lay, Julius G.
  - Lee, Ivy (Box 30)
  - Lehman, Robert
  - Levine, Isaac Don
  - Lewis, Edwin N.
  - Lindbergh, Charles A.
  - Lloyd George, David
  - Lochner, Louis P.
  - Long, Breckenridge
  - Lorimer, Mrs. George Horace
  - Lynd, Robert S.
  - "M" miscellaneous
  - MacAlarney, Robert Emmet
  - McCleary, J. T.
  - McGill, Ralph
  - McIntyre, Marvin H.
  - McKelway, B. M.
  - McNally, J. C.
  - Madden, Alec
  - Mallon, Mary Boland
  - Manca, Albino
  - Manning, William T.
  - Marcosson, Isaac F.
  - Mason, Edward F.
  - Mellon, Andrew W.
  - Merz, Charles (Box 31)
  - Meyer, Ernest L.
  - Meyer, Vincent
  - Miles, James
  - Miller, Paul
  - Miller, William E.
  - Millikan, Robert A.
  - Monroe, Arthur F.
  - Moore, Paul
  - Moran, John E.
  - Morgenthau, Henry (1856-1946)
  - Morley, Felix
  - Morris, Frederick M.
  - Moyers, Bill
  - Murray, Robert H.
  - "N" miscellaneous
  - Niblack, A. P.
  - Nicholson, Jane
  - Nicholson, Ralph
  - "O" miscellaneous
  - "P" miscellaneous
  - Parker, G. B.
  - Patton, George S. (1885-1945)
  - Payne, George Henry
  - Pegler, Westbrook
  - Phillips, William T.
  - Pike, James A.
  - Pinci, A. R.
  - Polk, Frank L.
  - Poole, DeWitt C.
  - Powell, Thomas Reed
  - Pringle, Henry F.
  - "R" miscellaneous (Box 32)
  - Reid, Helen Rogers
  - Rhine, J. B.
  - Roberts, Kenneth L.
  - Roberts, Roy A.
  - Robinson, Geroid Tanquary
  - Robinson, O. P.
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
  - Ross, Charles G.
  - Ryskind, Morris
  - "S" miscellaneous
  - Saito, Hirosi
  - Samborski, M. Robert
  - Sanger, Elliott M.
  - Scarlett, William
  - Schuster, M. Lincoln
  - Scott, Roderick
  - Seaman, Frank
  - Seymour, Charles
  - Shaw, Charles Gray
  - Sherman, M. S.
  - Sidener, Merle
  - Sloan, Alfred P.
  - Smith, Grace P.
  - Southam, W. M.
  - Speller, Robert
  - Sproul, William C.
  - Stagg, Jerry
  - Steinhardt, Laurence A.
  - Stettinius, Edward R.
  - Streit, Clarence K.
  - Strozier, Robert M.
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays
  - Swift, Otis Peabody
  - "T" miscellaneous
  - Taber, Grieg
  - Taft, William H. (Box 33)
  - Talbert, Ansel E.
  - Tebbel, John
  - Thams, Christian
  - Thompson, E. N.
  - Thompson, John
  - Thompson, S. A.
  - Thomson, Basil H.
  - Tisserant, Eugene Cardinal
  - Tobin, Richard L.
  - Tong, Hollington K.
  - Towns, Charles B.
  - Trexler, Samuel G.
  - Truman, Harry S.
  - Tumulty, Joseph P.
  - Tucker, Henry St. George
  - Twohey, James S.
  - Tyson, Levering
  - "U" miscellaneous
  - "V" miscellaneous
  - "W" miscellaneous
  - Waite, Clark F.
  - Walker, Harold
  - White, Andrew D.
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman
  - Willert, Arthur
  - Williams, Gaar
  - Williams, Maynard Owen
  - Williams, Talcott
  - Wilson, Edward C.
  - Wilson, Hugh R.
  - Wilson, Margaret Woodrow
  - Wiseman, William
  - Wrzos, Konrad
  - "Y" miscellaneous
  - Yalman, Ahmed Emin (Ahmet Emin)
  - Zelenko, Alexander V.
  - Unidentified, undated, and fragments
- Subject File, 1908-1970 (Box 34-158)
  Correspondence, memoranda, newspaper clippings, notes, printed material, and scrapbooks.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject and therein chronologically. A partial list of correspondents is provided for some of the subjects.
  - Ackerman (Carl W.) Inc., correspondence concerning discontinuance of public relations activities, 1927 (Box 34)
  - African wild game, motion picture of, 1924-1927, undated
    - Eastman, George
    - Klein, A. J.
    - Roosevelt, Kermit
    - Thams, Christian
  - American Arbitration Association
  - American Club, London, England
  - American Committee for Devastated France, 1923
    - Morgan, Anne
  - American Committee for Relief of German Children, 1923
  - American Institute of Public Opinion, 1936-1937, 1957
    - Gallup, George
  - American Newspaper Publishers Association, 1933-1950
    - Davis, Howard
    - Hanson, Elisha
    - Harris, E. H.
    - McCormick, Robert R.
    - Olson, Kenneth E.
  - American Society of Newspaper Editors, 1933-1965 (Box 35)
    - Howard, N. R.
    - Kirchhofer, A. H.
    - Lawrence, David
    - Marvin, Dwight
    - Wallace, Tom
    - Miscellany
    - World Free Press Mission (Box 36)
      - Great Britain, Jan. 1945
      - France, Jan. 1945
      - Belgium and Luxembourg, Jan. 1945
      - Italy, Feb. 1945
      - Greece, Feb. 1945
      - Egypt, Feb. 1945 (Box 37)
      - Palestine, Feb. 1945
      - Iran, Mar. 1945
      - USSR, Mar. 1945
      - China, Mar.-Apr. 1945 (Box 38)
      - India, Mar.-Apr. 1945
      - Philippines, Apr.-May 1945
      - Pearl Harbor, May 1945 (Box 39)
      - United Nations Conference, San Francisco, Calif., May 1945
      - Correspondence, Nov. 1944-Sept. 1945, undated
        - Bickel, Karl A.
        - Bloom, Sol
        - Brown, Sevellon
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray
        - Connally, Tom
        - Cooper, Kent
        - Ellard, Roscoe
        - Forrest, Wilbur
        - Forrestal, James
        - Howard, Roy Wilson
        - Knight, John S.
        - McGill, Ralph
        - MacLeish, Archibald
        - Marshall, George C.
        - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
        - Stettinius, Edward R.
        - Wiley, Alexander
        - Wrzos, Conrad
      - Miscellany
      - Miscellany (Box 40)
      - Notes, miscellaneous
      - Report, final
      - Travel documents
      - Truman, Harry S.
  - American Valuation Association, 1921-1927
    - Fordney, Joseph W.
    - Morrison, A. Cressy
    - Miscellany
    - Printed matter (Box 41)
    - Scrapbook
    - "The Tariff Reform Movement"
  - Arizona Publishing Co. v. D.C. O'Neill, Harold L. Cross (Box 42)
  - Armenia, 1920
  - Associated Press
    - 1925-1965
    - German surrender story, 1945
    - Managing Editors' Association
  - Association of Producers of Petroleum in Mexico, 1926
  - Atlantic Monthly, 1922-1941
    - Barber, Joseph, Jr.
    - Sedgwick, Ellery
  - Austria-Hungary, 1914-1918 (Box 43)
  - Banshees Silber Lady Award, 1944-1967
  - Belgium, 1914-1915
  - Bernstein, Herman
  - Bolivar, Simon
  - Bolshevism, 1919
  - Borah, William Edgar, speech, 22 Sept. 1935
  - Bradford, William (1663-1752)
  - Brazil, trip to, 1950-1951 (Box 44)
    - Brazil, University of
    - Johnson, Herschel V.
    - Vargas, Getulio (interview with)
    - Wrzos, Conrad
  - Bretherton, Cyril H., Lusitania claim, 1923 (Box 45)
  - Brooklyn-Manhattan Transit Corp.
    - Miscellany
    - Clippings book (Box 46)
      - Oct.-Dec. 1923
      - Jan.-June 1924 (Box 47)
      - June-Oct. 1924 (Box 48)
  - Brucker, Herbert (Box 49)
  - Cabot, John M.
  - Cabot (Maria Moors) Prize
    - Correspondence and clipping book
      - Vol. 1, 1939
        - Berle, A. A. (1895-1971)
        - Braden, Spruille
        - Brown, Sevellon
        - Dreyfus, Louis G.
        - Duggan, Laurence
        - Frost, Wesley
        - Hull, Cordell
        - Ridely, C. S.
        - Rowe, L. S.
        - Weddell, Alexander W.
      - Vol. 2, 1939
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray
        - Cabot, Godfrey L.
        - Cabot, John M.
        - Dreyfus, Louis G.
        - Gollan, José Santos
        - Quesada, Luis Miró
      - Vol. 3, 1940 (Box 50)
        - Bowers, Claude G.
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray
        - Cabot, John M.
        - Dennis, William Cullen
        - Edwards, Agustin
        - Gollan, José Santos
        - Howard, Roy Wilson
        - Miller, James I.
        - Santos, Enrique
        - Valle, Rafael Heliodoro
      - Vol. 4, 1941 (Box 51)
        - Bettencourt, Paulo
        - Bettencourt, Sylvia
        - Cabot, Godfrey L.
        - Davila, Carlos
        - Rivero, José Ignacio
        - Roosevelt, Eleanor
    - Clipping book
      - Vol. 5, 1941
    - Correspondence and clipping book (Box 52)
      - Vol. 6, 1942
        - Bohigas, Angel
        - Canham, Erwin D.
        - Lasplaces, Alberto
      - Vol. 7, 1943
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray
        - Cabot, Godfrey L.
        - Cue, Pedro
        - De Llano, Rodrigo
        - Tomlinson, Edward
      - Vol. 8, 1944 (Box 53)
        - McGeachy, Albert Victor
        - Ortega, Carlos Mantilla
        - Pinto, Miguel
    - Correspondence and clipping book
      - 1947
        - Aramayo, Carlos Victor
        - Camargo, Alberto Lleras
        - Vela, David
      - 1948-1949 (Box 54)
        - Bracker, Milton
        - Carvallo, Alfredo Silva
        - Castillo, José Santiago
        - Dantas, Orlando Ribeiro
        - Jones, Joseph L.
        - Larreta, Eduardo Rodriguez
        - Sanchez, Manuel Cisneros
      - 1950-1952
    - Miscellany, 1953-1955 (Box 55)
    - Award to Ackerman, 1956
    - Miscellany, 1956-1965
    - Programs, 1939-1952
  - Caribbean, trip, Daniel E. Barbey, trip (Box 56)
  - Censorship
  - Century Association
  - Chastenet, Jacques
  - Chemical Research in American Industry (Box 57)
    - Survey of origins, 1929
      - Returns to questionnaires covering years
        - 1854-1915
        - 1916-1926 (Box 58)
        - 1927-1929 (Box 59)
      - Miscellaneous returns to questionnaires
      - Printed matter
      - Recapitulation
      - Correspondence, 1955-1956
  - Chicago Tribune (Box 60)
  - Chicago Tribune annual spring luncheon, New York, N.Y., 1937-1953
  - Chile, visiting journalists from, 1941
  - China, Republic of (Box 61)
    - Miscellany
      - 1915-1919
      - 1919, 1931-1943, 1964 (Box 62)
    - Order of the Brilliant Star award, 1946, 1949, 1954-1955 (Box 63)
    - Post-Graduate School of Journalism, 1943-1945 See also Classified
      - Ackerman, Robert V.
        - Correspondence
        - Lecture
      - Chungking Reporter
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1943-1948, 1960, 1963
        - Baker, Richard T.
        - Gilbert, Rodney
        - Tong, Hollington K.
        - Weart, D. L.
      - Miscellany
      - Scrapbook, 1943-1944
    - Trip to, Dec. 1918-Jan. 1919 (Box 64)
  - Clemenceau, Georges, visit to the United States, 1922
  - Collier's
  - Columbia University, New York, N.Y.
    - Ackerman portrait fund, 1953-1970
    - Advisory Board Handbook, 1946
    - Alumni affairs, 1941-1966, undated
    - Alumni directories
      - 1939, 1947
      - 1956-1967 (Box 65)
    - American Assembly
    - American Press Institute
      - Correspondence
      - Miscellany
    - Announcements
      - 1917-1918, 1930-1935
      - 1935-1960 (Box 66)
    - Baker, Richard T., A History of the Graduate School of Journalism
      - 1954
        - Bliss, Robert Woods
        - Cooper, Kent
    - Barrett, Edward W.
      - 1956-1959
      - 1960-1968, undated (Box 67)
    - Brucker, Herbert
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray
      - Correspondence, 1930-1945
      - Printed matter
    - Coggeshall, Reginald
    - Columbia Associates
    - Correspondence and clipping book (Box 68)
      - Vol. 1, 1931
        - Appointment as dean, messages of congratulation
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray
        - Cunliffe, J. W.
        - Eastman, George
        - Fackenthal, Frank D.
        - Gordon, J. Bennett
        - Howard, Roy Wilson
        - MacAlarney, Robert Emmet
        - Reid, Howard C., "Impressions of a Hero"
        - Sloan, Alfred P.
      - Vol. 2, 1931 (Box 69)
        - Cooper, Charles P.
        - Finley, John H.
        - Hurst, Fannie
        - Lorimer, George Horace
        - Manning, William T.
        - Ochs, Adolph S.
        - Parker, G. B.
        - Pulitzer, Ralph
        - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
        - Sidener, Merle
      - Vol. 3, 1932 (Box 70)
        - Bellamy, Paul
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray
        - Cooper, Charles P.
        - Cooper, Kent
        - Draper, Arthur S.
        - Hawkes, H. E.
        - Howard, Roy Wilson
        - James, J. L.
        - Lawrence, David
        - MacAlarney, Robert Emmet
        - Markel, Lester
        - Pew, Marlen
        - Pitkin, Walter B.
        - Pulitzer, Joseph (1885-1955)
        - Pulitzer, Ralph
      - Vol. 4, 1932 (Box 71)
        - Armstead, George B.
        - Astor, Nancy
        - Bingay, Malcolm W.
        - Brown, James W.
        - Rukeyser, Merryle S.
        - Wiley, Louis
        - Williams, Maynard Owen
      - Vol. 5, 1933 (Box 72)
        - Armstead, George B.
        - Bingay, Malcolm W.
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray
        - Draper, Arthur S.
        - Frankfurter, Felix
        - Howe, Louis McHenry
        - Pulitzer Prize, 1933
        - Weston, Samuel P.
      - Vol. 6, 1933 (Box 73)
        - Abbot, Willis J.
        - American Newspaper Publishers Association
        - Bickel, Karl A.
        - Bingay, Malcolm W.
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray
        - Collins, Edward H.
        - Dabney, Virginius
        - Dennis, William Cullen
        - Erskine, John
        - Finley, John H.
        - Freeman, Douglas Southall
        - Gordon, J. Bennett
        - Harris, E. H.
        - Haskall, Henry J.
        - Krock, Arthur
        - Lowell, A. Lawrence
        - Mathews, William R.
        - Moley, Raymond
        - National Recovery Administration
        - Pennington, Levi T.
        - Reid, Albert T.
      - Vol. 7, 1933 (Box 74)
        - Barr, Stringfellow
        - Bellamy, Paul
        - Harris, E. H.
        - Hughes, Charles E.
        - La Guardia, Fiorello H.
        - McCormick, Robert R.
        - Mathews, William R.
        - Mayo, Charles H.
        - National Recovery Administration
        - Spargo, John
        - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays
        - Woollcott, Alexander
        - Yost, Casper S.
      - Vol. 8, 1934 (Box 75)
        - Abbot, Willis J.
        - Atwood, M. V.
        - Fleming, Frederic S.
        - Fraser, Leon
        - Harris, E. H.
        - Hearst, William Randolph
        - House, Edward Mandell
        - Luce, Henry R.
        - Manning, William T.
        - McCormick, Robert R.
        - Miles, Walter R.
        - Moley, Raymond
      - Vol. 9, 1934 (Box 76)
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray
        - David, Howard
        - Hoover, Herbert
        - McCormick, Robert R.
        - National Recovery Administration
        - Pew, Marlen
        - Pulitzer, Joseph (1885-1955)
        - Pulitzer Prize, 1934
        - Ruhl, Robert W.
      - Vol. 10, 1934 (Box 77)
        - Armstead, George B.
        - Bryan, John Stewart
        - Freeman, Douglas Southall
        - Hanson, Elisha
        - Harris, E. H.
        - James, Edwin L.
        - Lawrence, David
        - McCormick, Robert R.
        - National Recovery Administration
        - Streit, Clarence K.
        - Sweetser, Arthur
        - Von Wiegand, Karl H.
        - Wilcox, Grafton S.
      - Vol. 11, 1935 (Box 78)
        - Armstead, George B.
        - Bender, Robert J.
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray
        - Freeman, Douglas Southall
        - Harris, E. H.
        - NRA newspaper code
        - Sedgwick, Ellery
        - Shotwell, James T.
        - Waymack, W. W.
        - Williams, Samuel M.
      - Vol. 12, 1935 (Box 79)
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray
        - Cooper, Kent
        - Freeman, Douglas Southall
        - Harris, E. H.
        - Hawkes, Herbert E.
        - Kalina, Antonin S.
        - McCormick, Robert R.
        - McKenzie, Vernon
        - Montague, Gilbert H.
        - NRA newspaper code
        - Northwestern University, Evanston, Ill.
        - O'Hara, John F.
        - Pew, Marlen
        - Pulitzer, Joseph (1885-1955)
        - Pulitzer, Ralph
        - Pulitzer Prize, 1935
        - Richmond, University of, Richmond, Va.
        - Streit, Clarence K.
      - Vol. 13, 1935 (Box 80)
        - Bretherton, Cyril H.
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray
        - Early, Joseph J.
        - Fleming, Frederic S.
        - Gordon, J. Bennett
        - Grew, Joseph C.
        - Howard, Roy Wilson
        - Knox, Frank
        - Lehman, Herbert H.
        - Morrison, C. M.
      - Vol. 14, 1935-1936 (Box 81)
        - Barrett, James W.
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray
        - Cooper, Charles P.
        - Deutsch, Eberhard P.
        - Emin, Ahmet (Ahmed Emin Yalman)
        - Harris, E. H.
        - Millikan, Robert A.
        - O'Hara, John F.
      - Vol. 15, 1936 (Box 82)
        - Baker, Frank S.
        - Donovan, William J.
        - Hirota, Koki
        - Meyer, Eugene
        - Mott, John R.
      - Vol. 16, 1936 (Box 83)
        - Fleming, Frederic S.
        - Freeman, Douglas Southall
        - Howard, Roy Wilson
        - Knox, Frank
        - Meyer, Eugene
      - Vol. 17, 1935-1936 (Box 84)
        - Cabot, John M.
        - Dennis, William Cullen
        - Fraser, Leon
        - James, Edwin L.
        - McCormick, Robert R.
        - Meyer, Eugene
        - Pulitzer Prize, 1936
      - Vol. 18, 1936 (Box 85)
        - Baker, Frank S.
        - Barber, Joseph, Jr.
        - Dennis, William Cullen
        - Emin, Ahmet (Ahmed Emin Yalman)
        - Gunther, John
        - Harris, E. H.
        - Hoover, Herbert
        - Hough, Elizabeth Bowie
        - House, Edward Mandell
        - Hutchison, Charles F.
        - Kirchhofer, A. H.
        - Knox, Frank
        - Lawrence, James E.
        - Marvin, Dwight
        - Pew, Marlen
        - Poole, DeWitt Clinton
        - Roberts, Roy
        - Schuster, M. Lincoln
        - Swope, Herbert Bayard
        - Thomas, Wilbur K.
        - Tyler, Charles A.
        - Williams, Maynard Owen
    - Correspondence, miscellaneous (Box 86)
      - 1931-1943
      - 1944-1969, undated (Box 87)
    - Coykendall, Frederick, 1933-1945
    - Cunliffe, J. W., 1921, 1930
    - Development, Office of
      - 1948-1951, Davis, Paul H.
      - 1952-1955, undated (Box 88)
    - Dodge, M. Hartley, 1933-1958
    - Douglas, Archibald, 1932-1941
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1947-1953, undated (Box 89)
    - Fackenthal, Frank D., 1930-1956 (Box 90)
    - 50th anniversary celebration, 1963
      - Letters of congratulation
      - Miscellany
    - Financial report, 1931-1956
    - Heights
    - Independent Journal, 1933-1939 (Box 91)
    - Jacobs, Albert C., 1947-1950, undated (Box 92)
    - King, Willard V.
      - Ackerman correspondence, 1930-1942
      - Papers of, 1909-1950, and miscellaneous
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray
        - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
        - Fackenthal, Frank D.
    - Kirk, Grayson, 1949-1968
    - Krout, John A., 1950-1955
    - Memoranda, 1933-1956 (Box 93)
    - Miscellany
      - 1923-1943
      - 1944-1949 (Box 94)
      - 1950-1967, undated (Box 95)
    - Pitkin, Walter B., 1931-1950 (Box 96)
    - Retirement as dean, 1956
      - Correspondence and memoranda
      - Faculty resolution, 21 May 1956
      - Messages of congratulation
      - Miscellany
    - Taylor, Floyd, 1943-1946
    - World trip, Oct. 1935-Jan. 1936 (Box 97)
      - Correspondence
  - Country Gentlemen, 1918
  - Crosman, Ralph L., 1945
  - Cuba, trip to, 1944
    - Miscellany
    - Scrapbook
  - Curtis, J. Montgomery, 1967 (Box 98)
  - Curtis Publishing Co., 1966
  - Czechoslovakia, 1918, 1946-1949
  - Dewey, Thomas E., 1939
  - Dodd, Mead & Co., 1917-1919
  - Dothan Eagle, 1960-1963
  - Doubleday, Page & Co., 1918
  - Dutch Treat Club, New York, N.Y.
    - Correspondence, 1956-1959
    - Miscellany
      - 1932-1961
      - 1962-1969 (Box 99)
  - Earlham College, Richmond, Ind.
    - Correspondence, 1915-1962, undated
      - Bolling, Landrum R.
      - Dennis, William Cullen
      - Edwards, David M.
      - Kelly, Robert L.
    - Printed matter (Box 100)
    - Student correspondence, 1908-1911
    - Student papers
  - Eastman, George, 1927-1932, 1944, 1952, 1954, undated (Box 101)
    - Gerard, James W.
    - Solbert, Oscar N.
  - Eastman Kodak Co.
    - 1922-1927
      - Chrystal, Eugene
      - Cotsworth, Moses B.
      - Winton, Roy W.
    - 1927-1959 (Box 102)
      - Winton, Roy W.
      - Printed matter
  - 80th birthday, messages of congratulation, 1970
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1952-1960 (Box 103)
  - Erskine, John
  - Everybody's Magazine, 1919
  - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1938-1941
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1939
  - Flight Safety Foundation, 1959-1966, undated
    - Fairchild, Sherman
    - Talbert, Ansel E.
  - Foreign Press Association, 1943-1946 (Box 104)
  - France, miscellany, 1914-1918, 1937
  - Gallegos, Romulo, 1948, 1955
  - General Motors Corp.
    - Correspondence, 1931
      - Sloan, Alfred P.
      - Stettinius, Edward R.
    - Miscellany, 1930-1931, 1938
  - Gerard, James W., 1917-1951 (Box 105)
  - Germany
    - Miscellany
      - 1913-1915
      - 1916 (Box 106)
      - 1916-1918 (Box 107)
      - 1918 (Box 108)
    - Notes, World War I
    - Ration coupons, World War I
  - Ginzburg, Benjamin, Rededication to Freedom, 1958
  - Great Britain
    - Miscellany
      - 1914
      - 1915-1922, undated (Box 109)
  - Greater New York Fund, 1939
    - Blaine, James G.
  - Gridiron Club, Washington, D.C.
  - Haiti
  - Harding, Warren G.
  - Harper and Brothers
  - Harper's Magazine
  - Hawaii, trip to, 1962
  - Hoover, Herbert, The Problems of Lasting Peace, correspondence, 1942 (Box 110)
    - Gibson, Hugh
    - Hoover, Herbert
  - Hoover Library on War, Revolution, and Peace
  - Houghton Mifflin Co., 1930
  - House, Edward Mandell
  - Hutchins, Robert M.
  - Independent, 1917, 1919
  - Indianapolis Star, 1909-1910
  - Industrial unrest, miscellany, circa 1919
  - Institute of American Business, Bronson Batchelor, 1921-1925 (Box 111)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations
  - Inter-American Federation of Working Newspaper-men's Organizations, 1962
  - Inter-American Press Association, 1956-1957
  - International Cultural Cooperation Committee, 1963
  - Japan (Box 112)
    - Imperial family
    - Miscellany
      - 1917-1938
      - 1938-1950 (Box 113)
  - Journalism (Box 114)
    - Nineteenth-century history, Oswald Garrison Villard
      - Printed matter
        - 1911, 1923-1937
        - 1938-1970 (Box 115)
        - Undated (Box 116)
  - Kahn, Otto H., 1923-1926, undated
  - Kennedy, John F., Blauvelt family genealogy, 1962
  - King, Willard V., Franklin D. Roosevelt
  - Korea, 1918
  - La Guardia, Fiorello H.
  - Latin America
    - Miscellany, 1914-1958
    - Trips (Box 117)
      - 1937
        - Scrapbooks
          - Vols. 1-2
            - Dreyfus, Louis G.
            - Frost, Wesley
            - "The Invasion of South America" (typescript)
            - Jones, Joseph L.
            - Monroe, Arthur F.
            - Pan American Union
            - Stahlman, James G.
            - United States Department of State
            - Weddell, Alexander W.
          - Vol. 3 (Box 118)
      - Dec. 1941-Jan. 1942, miscellany
      - 1954-1955 (Box 119)
        - Scrapbook
          - Argentina
          - Brazil
          - Chile
          - Panama
          - Peru
          - Puerto Rico
          - Venezuela
          - Cabot, John M.
          - Cabot (Maria Moors) Prize
          - Columbia University, New York, N.Y.
        - Miscellany
  - League of Nations (Box 120)
    - Correspondence, Arthur Sweetser, 1921
    - Dispatches from Geneva concerning, 1920-1921
    - Miscellany
  - Lend-Lease Bill (H.R. 1776), 1941
    - Danaher, John A.
    - Wallace, Tom
    - Wheeler, Burton K.
  - Liverpool, England, trip, 1911
  - Lotos Club, New York, N.Y., 1917-1934
  - MacAlarney, Robert Emmet, 1914, 1945
  - McCloy, John J., 1949
  - Manchester Guardian, 1921
  - Marquis Who's Who, Inc., 1962-1965
  - Mayes, Herbert R., 1948
  - Mexico, 1917-1921 (Box 121)
    - Correspondence
    - Printed matter
  - Motion Picture Producers and Distributors of America, Inc.
    - Correspondence
      - Hays, Will H.
      - Klein, Julius
      - Zukor, Adolph
    - Printed matter
  - National Observer, 1962